{
    "subject": "Richard_Attenborough",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sheila_Sim",
    "human_readable": "Richard Attenborough is married to Sheila Sim.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9407165050506592,
            "question": "Is Richard Attenborough married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9337211847305298,
            "question": "Who is Richard Attenborough married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9308861494064331,
            "question": "To whom was Richard Attenborough married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9245391488075256,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Richard Attenborough and Sheila Sim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633291721343994,
            "question": "Was Richard Attenborough ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.828895092010498,
            "question": "Name a famous actor who was married to Sheila Sim."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7330409288406372,
            "question": "What is the name of Richard Attenborough's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7266395688056946,
            "question": "What is the name of Richard Attenborough's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6760047674179077,
            "question": "Richard Attenborough's wife is named...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6438282132148743,
            "question": "Who is Sheila Sim?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Richard Attenborough is married to Sheila Sim.",
            "html": "yago_18861_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Richard Attenborough's wife is named...?",
            "html": "yago_18861_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Richard Attenborough's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_18861_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Richard Attenborough's wife?",
            "html": "yago_18861_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18861_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Richard Attenborough is married to Sheila Sim\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe context information contains multiple documents that mention Richard Attenborough and Sheila Sim as a couple. Document paths `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_18861/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt`, `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_18861/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt`, `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_18861/re-ranker-msmarco/90.txt`, and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_18861/re-ranker-msmarco/82.txt` all mention that Sheila Sim was married to Richard Attenborough."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Sheila Sim was married to Richard Attenborough. For instance, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_18861/re-ranker-msmarco/90.txt` states: \"Sheila Beryl Grant Attenborough, The Lady Attenborough (n\u00e9e Sim; 5 June 1922 \u2013 19 January 2016), known professionally by her maiden name Sheila Sim, was an English film and theatre actress. She was the wife of the actor and director Richard Attenborough.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}